A Guide to the Pete Calos Photograph Collection, 1977-2005
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Pete Calos Photograph Collection, 1977-2005
The Library of Virginia
Prints and Photographs C1:111
884 Slides and 25 Compact Discs
Pete Calos, Photographer
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
A gift of Pete Calos to Special Collections, Library of Virginia in 1998, 2006.
Biographical Information
Pete Calos is a retired engineer from thirty-two years with Allied Chemical Corporation. Calos cultivated his passion for photography from an early age. He established the first photographic darkroom at George Wythe High School in Danville, and went on to document sports events for the Danville News. He attended V.P.I. Extension program for college prep, and graduated from Virginia Tech in Industrial Engineering in 1954. Later that year he entered the U.S. Army, serving three years, primarily in France.
Being familiar with travelogues from attending presentations at the Sheperd Center in Richmond, after retirement Calos began to write and illustrate his own presentations. Combining his interests in travel and photography Calos has created over sixty presentations on subjects found within Virginia, and several more on his tours of Europe, Russia, China, and the Mediterranean.
Scope and Content
The Pete Calos Photograph Collection is comprised of film duplicates of his original 35mm Ecktachrome color slides, and digital scans of original prints stored on compact discs. The images document architectural, environmental, commercial, and popular culture subjects in Virginia between 1977 and 2005. Images were selected, researched, and recorded by amateur photographer, Pete Calos for the purpose of illustrating over sixty slide lecture presentations. The collection holds significant interest for local and architectural historians. These images capture a moment in time, and in many cases represent the only visual document of historical buildings, streets and structures that have significantly changed or are no longer in existence. The collection is organized according to his original order in nine series which derive from his presentations: Bridges, Churches of Petersburg, Colonial Churches, Diners, Historic Churches, Lighthouses, Route One, Small Town U.S.A., W.P.A. Murals and the CD-Rom format series of mixed subjects.
I. Bridges series consists of images of closed, abandoned, deteriorating, and operating bridges located in Virginia. The topic was inspired by an article in the Richmond Times Dispatch, February 2001. The article stated that twenty-eight percent of Virginia's bridges were deficient, and more were destined for destruction. The article inspired Calos to capture twenty bridges slated for demolition in two days. Since that time, many have been torn down. Included in his lectures were his superlative bridge choices; the highest, lowest, longest, shortest, oldest, and newest bridges at the time. Some images date from the mid to late seventies, with the majority taken between Spring and Fall, 2001.
II. Colonial Churches series includes photographs of historically significant churches taken during 2005 in various locations across the state; Hanover Co., Fairfax Co., Hampton, James City Co., King William Co., Lancaster Co., Norfolk, Smithfield Co., Suffolk, Westmoreland Co., and Richmond Co.
III. Churches of Petersburg series documents the various denominations located in the downtown Petersburg area. Calos recorded views of the exterior, and significant interior architectural details during 2005.
IV. Richmond Historic Churches series covers significant churches, predominately in the downtown Richmond area taken (unless specifically noted) during 2002. Calos documented the exterior, and when access was allowed recorded the sanctuary, altar, and noteworthy architectural details.
V. Virginia Diners series include many establishments which have been in operation for fifty or more years. This theme was inspired by The Coney Island Lunch, a cafe diner begun by his father in 1919 in Danville, Virginia. Calos and other family members worked in the cafe which continued as a family business until December 31, 1971 when it became a victim of urban renewal after 52 years of service. This series documents many family run eateries, past and present in existence across the state during the period of 1996 to 2005. Calos has carefully recorded the characteristic architecture, the interior decor, restaurant fixtures, menus, advertisements, cuisine, as well as some portraits of original owners and staff.
VI. Lighthouses records active and historic Virginia lighthouses photographed by Calos from 1995 through 2003.
VII. The Route One series records the visual flavor of bygone hotels, businesses, homes, as well as current attractions along the Virginia section of this eastern seaboard roadway. Also known as U.S. Rt. 1 or Jefferson Davis Highway, the roadway opened in 1926. From 1997 to 2001 Calos recorded select locations of the Virginia portion, from Arlington in the North to Woodbridge in the South.
VIII. The Small Town U.S.A. series records the characteristic appearance of streets, businesses, and buildings that many small towns in Virginia share. The visual appeal of these images in Black and White was originally due to an error in the color film processing. But Calos accepted the gaffe as art by accident, and found the result as a fitting representation for the vintage nature of the subject.
IX. W.P.A. Murals document murals commissioned for Virginia Post Offices by the New Deal, Works Progress Administration's, Section of Fine Arts during 1934-1943. Popularly called The Section, it was headed by Edward Bruce, and administered by the Procurement Division of the Treasury Department. The program operated as incentive to put artisans to work during the Depression years by awarding commissions for murals in public buildings. Calos concentrated on recording existing murals in Post Offices throughout Virginia from 1997 to 2001.
X. The Calos Compact Disc Collection includes subjects captured from 1996 to 2001 during the photographer's travel through counties across Virginia. Subjects are mixed and include; abandoned homes, log cabins, Post Offices, schools, diners, stores, restaurants, bridges, views, hotels, taverns, theatres, barns, churches, cemeteries, courthouses, libraries, laundries, fire stations, railroad stations, service stations, drug stores, barber shops, and banks.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Bridges
Series II: Colonial Churches
Series III: Churches of Petersburg
Series IV: Richmond Historic Churches
Series V: Virginia Diners
Series VI: Lighthouses
Series VII: Route One
Series VIII: Small Town U.S.A.
Series IX: W.P.A. Murals
Series X: Compact Disc Collection
Contents List
- Series I: Bridges., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  The Bridge series was inspired by an article in the Richmond Times Dispatch, February 2001. The article revealed that twenty-eight percent of Virginia's bridges were deficient, and more were destined for destruction, statistics that inspired Calos to act. In documenting as many bridges as he could find, he made sure to record the superlatives; the highest, lowest, longest, shortest, oldest and newest bridges in the state at that time. The 140 color slides date from the mid to late seventies, with the majority taken between Spring and Fall of 2001.
  Maintained in original order:
  - Jackson River, Bath Co. - 27 August 1977 - (Othertype 1:1)
  - Rt. 11 South, Over North Fork of Shenandoah River - 19 October 1977 - (Othertype 1:2)
  - Rt. 626 Over Piggs River, Pittsylvania Co. - 15 May 1978 - (Othertype 1:3)
  - Rt. 880, Va Bridge & Iron Company, Pittsylvania Co. - 25 February 1978 - (Othertype 1:4)
  - Rt. 675 Over the River, Shenandoah Co. - 27 January 1979 - (Othertype 1:5)
  - Rt. 58, Roanoke Iron and Bridge Co., Grayson Co. - 7 June 1975 - (Othertype 1:6)
  - Poplar Mines, Amherst Co. - 24 March 1975 - (Othertype 1:7)
  - Rt. 752, Rockingham Co. - 7 April 1981 - (Othertype 1:8)
  - Natural Bridge - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:9)
  - Rockbridge County Foot Bridge - 4 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:10)
  - Rt. 1, Falling Creek - 11 April 2001 - (Othertype 1:11)
  - Danville Bridge - 25 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:12)
  - Rt. 1, Stone Creek Bridge, Dinwiddie Co. - 3 April 2001 - (Othertype 1:13)
  - Rt.733, Simple Beam Bridge Over Elk River - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:14)
  - Covered Bridge, Campbell Co. - 31 December 1978 - (Othertype 1:15)
  - Benjamin Harrison Bridge, James River - 22 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:16)
  - Benjamin Harrison Bridge and Barge - 22 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:17)
  - Enon Bridge - 15 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:18)
  - Off Rt. 40, Franklin Co. - 24 October 2001 - (Othertype 1:19)
  - Rt. 630, Mansion Camelback Bridge,(dismantled)Over Staunton River Pittsylvania Co. - 28 February 1998 - (Othertype 1:20)
  - Mansion Camelback Bridge, Pittsylvania Co. - 23 February 1998 - (Othertype 1:21)
  - Mansion Camelback Bridge, Pittsylvania Co. - 23 February 1998 - (Othertype 1:22)
  - Under Mansion Camelback Bridge showing river, Pittsylvania Co., - 23 February 1998 - (Othertype 1:23)
  - Copy photo of construction of Benjamin Harrison Bridge - 1966 - (Othertype 1:24)
  - Copy photo of Benjamin Harrison Bridge under construction with Rainbow over City Point, Hopewell - 1966 - (Othertype 1:25)
  - View of Benjamin Harrison Bridge from Boat with Onlookers - 15 May 1977 - (Othertype 1:26)
  - View of Benjamin Harrison Bridge with new tower 27 December 1977 (Othertype 1:27)
  - Benjamin Harrison Bridge With New Tower - 11 March 1978 - (Othertype 1:28)
  - Benjamin Harrison Bridge, completed construction - 7 August 1978 - (Othertype 1:29)
  - Chippenham I-95 Bridge, under construction - 9 March 2003 - (Othertype 1:30)
  - Chippenham I-95 Bridge, under construction - 9 March 2003 - (Othertype 1:31)
  - Chippenham I-95 Bridge, under construction - 9 March 2003 - (Othertype 1:32)
  - Rt. 895, Pocahontas Parkway construction - 21 May 2002 - (Othertype 1:33)
  - Pocahontas Parkway construction - 21 May 2002 - (Othertype 1:34)
  - Pocahontas Parkway, near completion - 21 May 2002 - (Othertype 1:35)
  - Rt. 613, Rappahannock River, Culpepper Co., oldest Bridge (1878) in Virginia - 20 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:36)
  - Dayton, Rockingham Co., Lowest Bridge in Virginia - 3 May 1993 - (Othertype 1:37)
  - Bridge over Maury River, Rockbridge Co., Highest in State - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:38)
  - Truss Bridge, Botetourt Co. - 4 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:39)
  - Little Calfpasture River, Augusta Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:40)
  - Rocky Mill Bridge, Lunenburg Co. - 2 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:41)
  - Rocky Mill Bridge with sign, Lunenburg Co. - 2 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:42)
  - Rocky Mill Bridge showing river, Lunenburg Co. - 2 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:43)
  - Rt. 677, Lunenburg and Mechlenburg Co. - 2 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:44)
  - Rt. 601 Aaron's Creek, Halifax and Mecklenburg Co. - 2 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:45)
  - Rt. 650, Cub Run, Rockingham Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:46)
  - Rt. 782, One Lane Bridge, Rockingham Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:47)
  - Rt. 782, One Lane Bridge, Rockingham Co., maker's mark - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:48)
  - Rt. 753 off Rt. 42, Wangers' Mill Rd.(Abandoned)at Linville Creek, Rockingham Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:49)
  - Linville Creek Bridge, Rt. 1421, Thacher Truss, Rockingham Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:50)
  - Thacher Truss, maker's mark - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:51)
  - Rt. 724 over North River, Mt. Crawford, Rockingham Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:52)
  - Rt. 724 over North River, Rockingham Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:53)
  - Rt. 769, Middle River, Augusta Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:54)
  - Rt. 769, Middle River, Augusta Co., maker's mark - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:55)
  - Rt. 775, Middle River, Augusta Co., - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:56)
  - Rt. 774, Middle River, August Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:57)
  - Rt. 774, Middle River, August Co., detail of girder - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:58)
  - Rt. 778 over Middle River, Augusta Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:59)
  - Rt. 778, over Middle River,August Co., maker's mark Champion Bridge Co. - 12 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:60)
  - Rt. 733 over Elk River, Augusta Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:61)
  - Rt. 733 over Elk River, Augusta Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:62)
  - Rt. 733 over Elk River, Augusta Co., mark Champion Bridge Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:63)
  - Rt. 733 over Elk River, Augusta Co., simple beam construction - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:64)
  - Rt. 801 over Jenkins, Augusta Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:65)
  - Rt. 683-4 Little Cowpasture River (closed), Augusta Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:66)
  - Rt. 683-4 Little Cowpasture River (closed), Augusta Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:67)
  - Rt. 42 and Rt. 39 Goshen, Cowpasture River, Rockbridge Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:68)
  - Rt. 746, Maury River, Rockingham Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:69)
  - Rt. 650, Southern Railroad Bridge, Nelson Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:70)
  - Rt. 650, Southern Railroad Bridge, Nelson Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:71)
  - Rt. 795 over Hardware River, Albemarle Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:72)
  - Rt. 795 over Hardward River, Albemarle Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:73)
  - Rt. 684, Powhatan Co. - 13 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:74)
  - Rt. 45, Cartersville, James River - 25 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:75)
  - Cartersville, Rt. 45, James River - 25 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:76)
  - Cartersville, Rt. 45, James River, Old and New - 25 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:77)
  - Rt. 613, Culpepper, Rappahannock River - 25 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:78)
  - Rt. 613, Culpepper, Rappahannock River - 25 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:79)
  - Rt. 613, Culpepper, Rappahannock River, bridge supports - 25 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:80)
  - Rt. 3, Rappahannock - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:81)
  - Rt. 3, Rappahannock - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:82)
  - Rt. 715, Gholson Bridge, Brunswick Co. - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:83)
  - Rt. 715, Gholson Bridge, Brunswick Co. - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:84)
  - Rt. 715, Gholson Bridge, Brunswick Co. - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:85)
  - Rt.1 Falling Creek Chesterfield - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:86)
  - Rt. 698, Henry's Mill Bridge, Halifax and Pittsylvania Co. - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:87)
  - Rt. 698, Henry's Mill Bridge, Halifax and Pittsylvania Co. - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:88)
  - Rt. 620, Clarkton, Charlotte and Halifax Co. (closed) - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:89)
  - Rt. 620, Clarkton, Roanoke River (Staunton) - 24 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:90)
  - Belmont Golf Course, Richmond and Henrico Co. - 16 May 2001 - (Othertype 1:91)
  - Belmont Golf Course, Richmond and Henrico Co. - 16 May 2001 - (Othertype 1:92)
  - Rt. 727 over Jackson River, Botetourt Co. - 16 May 2001 - (Othertype 1:93)
  - Rt. 727 over Jackson River, Botetourt Co. - 16 May 2001 - (Othertype 1:94)
  - Rt. 685, Phoenix Truss, Botetourt Co. - 4 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:95)
  - Rt. 685, Craig Creek, Phoenix Truss, maker's mark - 4 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:96)
  - Rt. 685, Craig Creek, Phoenix Truss, detail - 4 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:97)
  - South Buffalo Creek, Rockbridge Co. - 4 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:98)
  - Photographer Pete Calos and friend - 4 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:99)
  - Rt. 623 outside Pembroke, Giles Co. - 4 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:100)
  - Rt. 761 off 58, New River, Grayson Co. - 4 June 2001 - (Othertype 1:101)
  - Rt. 761 off 58, New River at Mouth of Wilson, Grayson Co. - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:102)
  - New River off Rt. 761, River Falls Grayson Co. - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:103)
  - Rt. 715 S. Gholson Bridge, Brunswick Co., maker's mark Wrought Iron Bridge Co., Canton, OH - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:104)
  - Rt. 715 S. Gholson Bridge, Brunswick Co. - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:105)
  - Rt. 727, Botetourt Co., Calos on Bridge over Jackson River - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:106)
  - Worsham Street Railroad Bridge, Danville - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:107)
  - Worsham Street Railroad Bridge, Danville, horseshoe - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:108)
  - Worsham Street Bridge, Main Street Danville - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:109)
  - Worsham Street Bridge, Main Street Danville, cracked balustrade - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:110)
  - Worsham Street Bridge, Main Street Danville, dedication mark - 16 August 2001 - (Othertype 1:111)
  - Under the Powhite Bridge, Kanawha Canal - 22 March 2001 - (Othertype 1:112)
- Series II: Colonial Churches., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  The photographs of Colonial Churches were taken in 2005 to document the historically significant churches of that period in various locations across the state; Hanover Co., Fairfax Co., Hampton, James City Co., King William Co., Lancaster Co., Norfolk, Smithfield Co., Suffolk, Westmoreland Co., and Richmond Co.
  - Slash Christian Church- Hanover Co, Rt. 657 (Othertype 1:113)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church- Hanover County (Othertype 1:114)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church- Hanover County- stained glass window (Othertype 1:115)
  - Mangohick Baptist Church- King William Co., Rt. 30 (Othertype 1:116)
  - Immanuel Episcopal- Old Church, Hanover County (Othertype 1:117)
  - Immanuel Episcopal- Old Church Hanover County- interior pews (Othertype 1:118)
  - Aquia Church - door entry (Othertype 1:119)
  - Aquia Church - tiered pulpit (Othertype 1:120)
  - Aquia Church - sanctuary (Othertype 1:121)
  - Aquia Church - pedestal (Othertype 1:122)
  - Aquia Church - sanctuary (Othertype 1:123)
  - Pohick Episcopal Church - Fairfax County (Othertype 1:124)
  - Pohick Episcopal Church - Fairfax County - door entry (Othertype 1:125)
  - Pohick Episcopal Church - Fairfax County- sanctuary (Othertype 1:126)
  - Pohick Episcopal Church - Fairfax County - pulpit (Othertype 1:127)
  - Christ Church - (Othertype 1:128)
  - Christ Church - pulpit (Othertype 1:129)
  - Presbyterian Meeting House - (Othertype 1:130)
  - Presbyterian Meeting House - (Othertype 1:131)
  - Presbyterian Meeting House - (Othertype 1:132)
  - Presbyterian Meeting House - pipe organ (Othertype 1:133)
  - Presbyterian Meeting House - interior (Othertype 1:134)
  - St. John's, Hampton - (Othertype 1:135)
  - St. John's - Hampton - altar (Othertype 1:136)
  - St. John's - Hampton - aisle (Othertype 1:137)
  - St. John's - Hampton- stained glass of St. Michael (Othertype 1:138)
  - St. John's - Hampton- stained glass of Baptism of Pocahontas (Othertype 1:139)
  - St. Paul's - Norfolk (Othertype 1:140)
  - St. Paul's - Norfolk -entry (Othertype 1:141)
  - St. Paul's - Norfolk- stained glass of Paul Preaching (Othertype 1:142)
  - St. Luke's Chapel - Smithfield - exterior (Othertype 1:143)
  - St. Luke's Chapel - Smithfield - interior (Othertype 1:144)
  - St. Luke's Chapel - Smithfield - stained glass of St. Luke (Othertype 1:145)
  - St. Luke's Chapel - Smithfield - exterior of apse showing stained glass (Othertype 1:146)
  - St. Luke's Chapel - Smithfield - showing vaulted ceiling beams and stained glass (Othertype 1:147)
  - St. John's of Chuckatuck - exterior (Othertype 1:148)
  - Weycomico Church - Westmoreland County- exterior (Othertype 1:149)
  - Weycomico Church - Westmoreland County - exterior side front of door and brick columns (Othertype 1:150)
  - Weycomico Church - Westmoreland County - exterior entry door (Othertype 1:151)
  - Weycomico Church - Westmoreland County - entrance and sundial (Othertype 1:152)
  - North Farnham Church - Richmond County - exterior (Othertype 1:153)
  - North Farnham Church - Richmond County - exterior (Othertype 1:154)
  - St. Mary's White Chapel - entrance (Othertype 1:155)
  - Christ Church - Lancaster County - entrance (Othertype 1:156)
  - Christ Church - Lancaster County - from interior looking out front door (Othertype 1:157)
  - Bruton Parish - steeple (Othertype 1:158)
  - Bruton Parish - front entrance (Othertype 1:159)
  - Bruton Parish - exterior (Othertype 1:160)
  - Hickory Neck Church- Rt. 60, Toano (Othertype 1:161)
  - Hickory Neck Church - Rt. 60, Toano (Othertype 1:162)
  - Fork Church - Hanover County (Othertype 1:163)
  - Fork Church - Hanover County - entrance (Othertype 1:164)
- Series III: Petersburg Churches., Extent: 1 cabinet. (Othertype 1)
  Theses photographs document buildings in the downtown Petersburg area, presently owned by a variety of religious groups and denominations. Calos images capture the skyline of downtown, and record significant architectural details of both the churches' interior and exterior during his visits to Petersburg from December of 2003 to March 2004.
  - View of St. Stephens Episcopal, Trinity Missionary and House of Restoration - Petersburg skyline - (Othertype 1:165)
  - United Methodist Church - Washington Street - (Othertype 1:166)
  - United Methodist Church - Washington St. - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:167)
  - United Methodist Church-Washinton St. - stained glass of Good Shepherd - (Othertype 1:168)
  - United Methodist Church -Washington St. - Tiffayny glass, St. John - (Othertype 1:169)
  - United Methodist Church - Washington St. -stained glass of The Boy Samuel - (Othertype 1:170)
  - United Methodist Church - Washington St. - Jesus Preaching to the Multitude - (Othertype 1:171)
  - United Methodist Church - Washington St. -Christ before Pontius Pilate - (Othertype 1:172)
  - United Methodist Church - Washington St. - Garden of Gethsemane - (Othertype 1:173)
  - United Methodist Church - Washington St. - Three Kings - (Othertype 1:174)
  - United Methodist Church - Washington St. - Ten Commandments - (Othertype 1:175)
  - Tabb Street Presbyterian Church - (Othertype 1:176)
  - Tabb Street Presbyterian Church- detail of iron railing - (Othertype 1:177)
  - Tabb Street Presbyterian Church - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:178)
  - Tabb Street Presbyterian Church - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:179)
  - Tabb Street Presbyterian Church - organ and plaster ceiling medallion - (Othertype 1:180)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - steeple front - (Othertype 1:181)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:182)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - altar and stained glass - (Othertype 1:183)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - I know my redeamer liveth - stained glass - (Othertype 1:184)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal -Charity - stained glass - (Othertype 1:185)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - Christ - stained glass - (Othertype 1:186)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - Nativity - stained glass - (Othertype 1:187)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - Jesus - stained glass - (Othertype 1:188)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - Good Fight - stained glass - (Othertype 1:189)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - stained glass - (Othertype 1:190)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - stained glass World War II commemoration - (Othertype 1:191)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal - Communion- stained glass - (Othertype 1:192)
  - St. Joseph's Catholic Church - view of city (Othertype 1:193)
  - St. Joseph's Catholic Church - stained glass - (Othertype 1:194)
  - St. Joseph's Catholic Church - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:195)
  - St. Joseph's Catholic Church - Saints - stained glass - (Othertype 1:196)
  - St. Joseph's Catholic Church - Good Sheppard - stained glass - (Othertype 1:197)
  - St. Joseph's Catholic Church - Baptism - stained glass - (Othertype 1:198)
  - St. Joseph's Catholic Church - stained glass - (Othertype 1:199)
  - First Baptist Church - 235 N. Washington Street - (Othertype 1:200)
  - First Baptist Church - 235 N. Washington Street - (Othertype 1:201)
  - First Baptist Church - 235 N. Washington Street - sanctuary - (Othertype 1:202)
  - Second Presbyterian Church - W. Washington Street - (Othertype 1:203)